<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="privacy_policy_long">
        Privacy Policy for %4$s\n
        Effective Date: July 5, 2025\n
        Developer: %1$s\n
        App Name: %4$s\n\n

        1. Overview\n
        %4$s is a privacy-focused app that records accurate location data on your device. This privacy policy explains how your data is handled. In short: your data stays on your device and is never uploaded, shared, or collected by the developer.\n\n

        2. Data Collection and Usage\n
        Location Data\n
        The app collects your device’s location data with your permission. This data is:\n
        - Stored only locally on your device.\n
        - Never transmitted to any external servers.\n
        - Never accessible to the app developer or third parties.\n\n

        Storage\n
        All collected and derived data is saved in local SQLite databases on your phone. You have full control over this data.\n\n

        Export\n
        The app provides a manual export feature that allows you to share the raw database of the collected location data via Android’s share menu (e.g. to Google Drive, email, etc.). These exports are:\n
        - Triggered only by the user.\n
        - Unencrypted.\n
        - Entirely under your control.\n\n

        3. Data Sharing\n
        %4$s does not:\n
        - Send any data to remote servers.\n
        - Use third-party analytics.\n
        - Use any form of tracking.\n
        - Require a user account or login.\n\n

        Your data is never shared with the developer or any third party.\n\n

        4. Permissions\n
        %4$s may request the following Android permissions:\n
        - Location: To record your GPS position while logging.\n
        - Storage access: To read imported files and to save exported files if you choose to import or export your data.\n\n

        All permissions are requested transparently and only used for their intended purpose.\n\n

        5. Data Retention and Deletion\n
        All data is stored locally on your device and remains there until you choose to delete the app or manually delete the data within it.\n
        You can delete all collected data at any time by:\n
        - Clearing app data via your device settings.\n
        - Uninstalling the app.\n\n

        6. Children’s Privacy\n
        %4$s is not intended for use by children under 13. The app does not knowingly collect any data from children.\n\n

        7. Contact\n
        If you have any questions about this privacy policy, you can contact the developer at:\n
        Email: %2$s\n
        Website: %3$s\n\n
    </string>
</resources>
